SELWYN EZEKHIEL PARAS

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

09673

09673881201

 \boxtimes

Ezekhielofficial@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ezekhiel-paras-b67004157/

 \bigcirc

Tarlac City, Philippines

SKILLS

HTML, Laravel, Cloud Dev, PHP, Python, JavaScript, Wordpress, SEO, Linux, Django, Docker

Proficient English Speaker

Fast Learner

EDUCATION

Tarlac State University

2019-2022

AMA Computer College

2017-2019

ICT Colleges

Technical Vocational Course NCII 2017-2019

LANGUAGES

English

PROFILE

As a web developer, I have a strong foundation in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP, with a focus on creating user-friendly and visually appealing websites. I have experience designing and developing responsive websites, ecommerce sites, and content management systems. My proficiency in web design and development allows me to create custom websites that are optimized for search engines to improve their overall online presence.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Freelance (Self employed)

2017-2018

- I have developed a lot of projects by freelancing, Some of which are made in
 python using the django framework with tensorflow that analyzes parking
 spaces and transmit it to the mobile devices of the drivers. I've also created a ecommerce website named Cacaolavezares.com and still continues to accept
 small projects on my free time
- Created Applications for local businesses such as Point of sale system and inventory management system

Web Developer

Woebisoft Innovative Solutions

2018-2020

- Along side with universal vision, I have worked as a Freelance web developer for a company which out source customer and handed me the job.
- I have learned a lot working with them and other programmers working on projects
- Created Ecommerce website for a local company

Search Engine Optimization Specialist

Majorel

2022-2023

- I was a Search engine optimization support and specialist for Microsoft Advertising which helps new advertisers optimize their account for maximum conversions and reach of customer.
- I have also improved the system by automating the noting process incase the customer has reached back on a different advocate they will know what went through on the past issue
- I have above passing metrics since the day I was hired which gave me incentives

Web Developer

market role asia pacific inc

2023-2023

- I was a lead web developer for a marketing company
- I was assigned to create a rmtp server and run it on a vps could server
 on a docker container also deployed kubernetes for load balancing also
 deployed on the same cloud webhosting a websocket server
 specifically php laravel websockets for live chat implementation on the
 live streaming website which is Nacomex.com
- I was also the web developer and SEO specialist for the news website
 of the company Golasazo.com and Futbolfantastico.com which has
 reached 1.1k organic traffic within 1 month of my employment and
 developed it using wordpress I have also developed Plugins for our
 website due to the niche conten